<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="hello">Hello World, Memorizor!</string>
	<string name="app_name">Family Proc</string>
	<string name="btntxtFamProc1">Fam Proc 1</string>
	<string name="btntxtOldTest">Old Testament</string>
	<string name="btntxtGeBuAdrs">GeBuAdrs</string>
	<string name="tvCorrect">Correct: 0</string>
	<string name="tvWrong">Wrong: 0</string>
	<string name="strPartial">Wrong: 0</string>
	<string name="strwhtGeBuAdrs">Four score and seven years ago our fathers brought
		forth on this continent a new nation, conceived in liberty, and
		dedicated to the proposition that all men are created equal. Now we
		are engaged in a great civil war, testing whether that nation, or any
		nation, so conceived and so dedicated, can long endure. We are met on
		a great battle-field of that war. We have come to dedicate a portion
		of that field, as a final resting place for those who here gave their
		lives that that nation might live. It is altogether fitting and proper
		that we should do this. But, in a larger sense, we can not dedicate,
		we can not consecrate, we can not hallow this ground. The brave men,
		living and dead, who struggled here, have consecrated it, far above
		our poor power to add or detract. The world will little note, nor long
		remember what we say here, but it can never forget what they did here.
		It is for us the living, rather, to be dedicated here to the
		unfinished work which they who fought here have thus far so nobly
		advanced. It is rather for us to be here dedicated to the great task
		remaining before us, that from these honored dead we take increased
		devotion to that cause for which they gave the last full measure of
		devotion, that we here highly resolve that these dead shall not have
		died in vain, that this nation, under God, shall have a new birth of
		freedom, and that government of the people, by the people, for the
		people, shall not perish from the earth.</string>
	<string name="strwhtFamProc1">We, the First Presidency and the Council of the
		Twelve Apostles of The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints,
		solemnly proclaim that marriage between a man and a woman is ordained
		of God and that the family is central to the Creator\'s plan for the
		eternal destiny of His children. All human beings, male and female,
		are created in the image of God. Each is a beloved spirit son or
		daughter of heavenly parents, and, as such, each has a divine nature
		and destiny. Gender is an essential characteristic of individual
		premortal, mortal, and eternal identity and purpose. In the premortal
		realm, spirit sons and daughters knew and worshiped God as their
		Eternal Father and accepted His plan by which His children could
		obtain a physical body and gain earthly experience to progress toward
		perfection and ultimately realize his or her divine destiny as an heir
		of eternal life. The divine plan of happiness enables family
		relationships to be perpetuated beyond the grave. Sacred ordinances
		and covenants available in holy temples make it possible for
		individuals to return to the presence of God and for families to be
		united eternally.</string>
	<string name="strwhtOldTest">Genesis Exodus Leviticus Numbers Deuteronomy Joshua
		Judges Ruth 1Samuel 2Samuel 1Kings 2Kings 1Chronicles 2Chronicles Ezra
		Nehemiah Esther Job Psalms Proverbs Ecclesiastes Song_of_Solomon
		Isaiah Jeremiah Lamentations Ezekiel Daniel Hosea Joel Amos Matthew
		Mark Luke John Acts Romans 1Corinthians 2Corinthians Galatians
		Ephesians Philippians Colossians 1Thessalonians 2Thessalonians
		1Timothy 2Timothy Titus Philemon Hebrews James 1Peter 2Peter 1John
		2John 3John Jude Revelation</string>
</resources>
